

UX/UI DESIGNER





+27 65 571 1368



Iskenqa@gmail.com



Click to visit my portfolio

WORK EXPERIENCE

October 2020 -Present Atara Studios

Johannesburg

Conduct user-centered design research and analysis, and design user interfaces and user experiences for web and mobile applications

Proven track record designing websites and developing web apps, UI/UX design & brand identity for brands and

UX/UI Designer

Sep 2021 - Present Bukanindalo NPC

Remote

> IT Practitioner

organizations

In charge of all digital media components: administration, branding, social media management, web & email, design, promo apparel

EDUCATION HISTORY

2023 - Present Google

Remote

2022 Varsity College

Port Elizabeth

2021 MTN Business App Academy Remote

- Certificate Google UX
 Design Professional
 Certificate
- Higher Certificate Mobile
 Application & Web
 Development
- Higher Certificate MobileApplication Development

PROFILE

Using the infrastructure of technology, assist organizations to expand reach, increase accessibility and maintain a credible and reliable online presence. I specialize in UX/UI design and web development. I'm currently working on a UX case study for an Indian ed-tech startun

MY SKILLS

Web Development

JavaScript

HTM

CSS

Bootstrac

SASS

Gi+

Design

Figma

Webflow

WordPress

Shonify

Fiama

Adobe XD

Adobe InDesign

TRAITS

Creative

Communicator

Laser-focused

Team Playe